[
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tactica",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2641.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tektika",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2641.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.2",
        "question": "Zoom into the UAE.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15328.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.2",
        "question": "Zoom into the United Arab Emirates.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15328.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial ports in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6975.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial quotes in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6975.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial pots in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6975.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "commercials ports in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6975.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Port Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_530.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Kalifaport Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_530.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Pot Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_530.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.5",
        "question": "For the ships currently here, What is their  vessel movement for the last 24 hours?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14381.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the port itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19702.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the port itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19702.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pot itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19702.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pod itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19702.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Enhance the optical imagery and detect all ships",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15417.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Inhale the optical imagery and detect all shapes.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15417.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Enhance the imagery and detect all ships",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15417.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What assets are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5110.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5110.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5110.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.9",
        "question": "How many staff and visitors are within the port area?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12821.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.10",
        "question": "What is the water depth in the port area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10448.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.11",
        "question": "Provide a 3D visualization of the port's underwater topography",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_723.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.12",
        "question": "Yes, get the image",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4783.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.13",
        "question": "What is the latest known information about this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15991.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.14",
        "question": "What is the trajectory of this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2016.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.15",
        "question": "Open and analyse the new image\nDetect and identify the ships new location and any other suspected activity of the ship",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3795.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.16",
        "question": "Generate a report on these two ships and send it to Khalid",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15441.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.17",
        "question": "Yes. Also open the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4810.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.18",
        "question": "Close the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12428.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.19",
        "question": "Yes,  Lets look at the urban areas of Abu Dhabi, Zoom into Khalifa City and do land cover classification.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9039.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.20",
        "question": "What are the newly constructed buildings in Khalifa City in 2024?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4553.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.21",
        "question": "How many vehicles are in the imagery in this area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5054.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.22",
        "question": "Identify all palm trees in the region and surrounding main roads.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10167.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.23",
        "question": "Run red weevil analysis on the palm trees.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14898.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.24",
        "question": "What is the current traffic density around the region?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_237.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.25",
        "question": "Zoom into Zayed airport?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15319.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.26",
        "question": "Identify all airplanes and what is their operational activity.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3830.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.27",
        "question": "Identify all A380 airplanes in the airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1735.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.28",
        "question": "Zoom into the one connected to the terminal.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3302.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.29",
        "question": "Run model logic analysis on the airplane.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_6272.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.30",
        "question": "Generate a 3D of the Airbus A380",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17964.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.31",
        "question": "Do you have high frequency imagery over the airport?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19372.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.32",
        "question": "What are the changes in the western runway over the last 1 hour",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4231.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.33",
        "question": "Put and explain the thermal imagery.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2852.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.34",
        "question": "Standby",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10220.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.35",
        "question": "What kind of data can the system support? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19235.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.36",
        "question": "Open the notification tab",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14282.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.2",
        "question": "Tactica, generate and zoom-in into an area of interest 900 kilometers  West to East by 350 kilometers North to South, centered over the Straits of Hormuz",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11874.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.2",
        "question": "Tektika, generate and zoom-in into an area of interest 900 kilometers  West to East by 350 kilometers North to South, centered over the Straits of Hormuz",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11874.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.3",
        "question": "Identify all Naval ports, military, and dual-use airfields within the area of interest.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4669.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.3",
        "question": "Identify all Naval pots, military, and dual-use airfields within the area of interest.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4669.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.4",
        "question": "Identify all island-based fixed coastal defensive and anti-shipping installations ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10482.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.5",
        "question": "Identify and generate all fixed and mobile surface to air missile systems and aerial surveillance sites.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9818.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.6",
        "question": "Tactica, Which airfield has the most military activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.6",
        "question": "Tektika, Which airfield has the most military activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.6",
        "question": "Which airfield has the most military activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.7",
        "question": "Zoom into the airport and tell me. What satellite imagery do you have over this airport? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13827.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.8",
        "question": "Using the most recent high-resolution optical image, identify all military aircraft types at this airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17082.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.9",
        "question": "Is it operational?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.10",
        "question": "Why is there no optical imagery from the last week?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15119.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.11",
        "question": "analyze the latest two sar imagery ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19243.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.11",
        "question": "analyze the latest two-star imagery ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19243.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.12",
        "question": "Generate a 3D representation of F4 Phantom. ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19725.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.13",
        "question": "What about Bandar Abbas International Airport? Identify all military airplanes there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12644.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.14",
        "question": "Can Bandar Abbas operate and house Iran\u2019s recently purchased SU-35 Flanker aircraft?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3983.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.15",
        "question": "Can you elaborate on the Shelters part?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2476.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.16",
        "question": "What are the specifications of the SU-35 Flanker?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7356.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.17",
        "question": "Is it a threat to UAE military forces if deployed from Bandar Abbas or Konarak Airports?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14767.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.17",
        "question": "The Z-TEP threat to UA military forces if deployed from Banda Abbas or Konurak Airpods.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14767.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.18",
        "question": "Where was the latest location where the SU-35 has been detected within the area of interest?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7303.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.19",
        "question": "To what rank",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17121.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.40",
        "question": "NPPAlert",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16346.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.20",
        "question": "Yes. Give more information about the NPP Alert.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2636.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.20",
        "question": "Yes. Give more information about the NPT Alert.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2636.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.21",
        "question": "I dont know much about this location. What is BNPP?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13762.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.22",
        "question": "Show me more information about all the latest changes? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8200.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.23",
        "question": "Generate and open the report on the Power Plant.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3125.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.24",
        "question": "Close it, Label it as restricted, share it with my supervisor and archive it. Also, increase thermal coverage of the area.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2681.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.25",
        "question": "Thank you.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8289.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.26",
        "question": "Take me to Bandar Abbas Naval port and show me the imagery there.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16821.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7369.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.27",
        "question": "Tell me more about this pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_7369.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.28",
        "question": "Using this imagery, identify all naval ships within the naval port of Bandar Abbas",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_657.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.28",
        "question": "Using this imagery, identify all naval ships within the naval pot of Bandar Abbas",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_657.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.29",
        "question": "Using the last optical imagery,  what changes are occurring within the naval port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17624.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.29",
        "question": "Using the last optical imagery,  what changes are occurring within the naval pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17624.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.30",
        "question": "Highlight the changes using the latest sar with listing them and if there is any abnormal activity?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19669.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.31",
        "question": "I am interested in the IRGC area. What military equipment is present in the IRGC area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1661.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.32",
        "question": "Zoom into the training and label each unit",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4919.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.33",
        "question": "What changes are observed in sar and optical imagery?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15346.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.34",
        "question": "Is there any operational activity happening here? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17007.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.35",
        "question": "What are your recommendations for the departed ships?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10892.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.36",
        "question": "Identify all military ships in the last optical imagery in Area 1 and label.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13210.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.37",
        "question": "Why are these ships there?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10914.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.38",
        "question": "Zoom into the Bagheri drone ship and provide more information",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14315.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.38",
        "question": "Zoom into the Bikari drone ship and provide more information.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14315.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "2.39",
        "question": "Standby",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15351.mp3"
    }
]